Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
emos
clue
guy
クオ
Flo
Thank you.
Some time after the two met, the Black Bulls were sent out on a dungeon-clearing mission.
They battled a Diamond Kingdom mage named Mars, and Asta was gravely injured.
Noelle had gone out to gather restorative herbs for her wounded squadmate.
Come on, where is it?
That's the one?
Excuse me.
You there with the silver hair?
Yes, hello.
Do you have a second?
I'm sorry to bother you, but it won't take long.
I just wanted a closer look at something of yours.
Like I said, it'll only take a second.
Why, you?
What?
You hurt!
Wait, no, it's not like that!
Please, I swear!
Oh, yeah, then what is it like, huh?
How's a man supposed to get a decent nap with all this screaming going on?
Is that Noelle?
Shut up!
Don't let him touch me!
You've got it all wrong, I'm not some kind of creep.
I just want a real quick look.
Please, I'm even willing to pay you.
Just a peek, that's all.
Oh.
Feel my wrath!
Pan is only one letter away from pain!
Poor thing, it must have been so frightening
being set upon by a vile man like that.
What were you trying to do to her?
She came running in, scared out of her mind.
You're lucky we busted you up instead of killing you.
Please, it's not how it looks.
I was robbed, that's why.
Nobody wants to hear it, freak.
We should let him loose, then we can capture him again!
You don't deserve to live in the same world as Marie.
Now die.
Yes, Knight's Headquarters, this is Finral reporting for the Black Bulls.
We have a pervert in custody here, and we'll be bringing him in at once.
No, please don't.
I can explain, this is a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding works at the tavern, I think.
I think we're having some communication issues.
Zell?
Hold on.
Asta?
Whoa, you're not looking so good, are you okay?
Sort of.
But enough about me, it seems you made it into a Magic Knight squad.
Congratulations.
Hmm.
So it was all a misunderstanding?
You were robbed and they took your clothes?
You could have told us that earlier.
I tried, but you weren't exactly in a listening mood.
Yeah, details, details, who cares?
Here you go.
It's like I always say, better bread than dead.
Oh, sure, thanks.
We don't get new friends very often.
I hope you'll tell me more about yourself.
What's wrong?
Zell, I gotta say, you look pretty familiar.
Have we met somewhere before?
Oh, no.
I think I would remember meeting you.
How'd you end up at her hideout anyway, old man?
Oh, I forgot.
Excuse me, but you're Noelle, aren't you?
I'm really sorry for frightening you like that.
I wanted to ask you about your wand, that's all.
That's what you wanted to see?
Yes.
I think I know it's Maker.
A woman named Domina I've been seeking for a while now.
Domina?
I remember that name.
She's your fiancée, isn't she?
All right.
But I don't think she made this.
The person who gave it to me was named Code.
Doesn't sound like this Domina you're looking for.
It is, though.
It's her.
You see, her full name is actually Dominante Code.
Where did you get it?
From a stall in the Castletown's Black Market.
The Castletown.
Thank you.
Domina's alive!
That's awesome news, Zell!
Well, go get her!
What are you waiting for?
You're right.
I should go.
Right now.
Thank you.
I can take you there.
Noelle, listen.
Because of you, I'm going to be reunited with the woman I love.
Finally.
Thank you.
I didn't do anything, though.
Captain, sir, am I free to leave now?
Yeah, sure, why not?
But don't go blabbing about how we falsely imprisoned you.
You're the one talking about false imprisonment.
Shut it, portal boy.
Well, speaking of which, use your spatial magic to send them on their way.
Then we'll be square.
I need a dump and a nap.
I appreciate it.
I should get going or it's going to be too hard to say goodbye.
See ya, Asta.
I'm glad our paths crossed again, even if it wasn't for long.
Now, go out and become the Wizard King.
Sure thing!
And you go and live happily ever after.
Everyone, get down!
Huh?
Oh, cool!
Someone's attacking us!
It's probably the people who were after me.
So, sounds like it's time to get out of here.
Uh-oh.
What the hell is this?
Whoever woke me up just turned themselves a-killin'.
There's been no movement so far.
Strange Master Fonzel didn't leave at once.
That's what I would have expected him to do.
For now, let's watch and wait.
Squads one through four, maintain your formation and begin a steady advance.
Squads five and six, continue to stand ready at the rear.
That building.
It looks like some sort of dormitory.
Yes.
I ought to be on my way now, Commander Galio.
A portal, if you wouldn't mind.
You want a little insurance in case our sneak attack fails.
Huh.
I honestly don't know what you're so worried about.
We'd be a real laughingstock if we couldn't pull off an operation like this.
I'm not sure I like your attitude.
You remember who allowed you to live, right?
I'm aware that I owe you my life, Commander.
And don't forget it.
Since I'm in your debt, I'll offer you a little advice.
Defeating my old teacher won't be easy.
Squad one, scout reporting.
We're within 65 feet of the building.
Good.
Prepare to charge.
The target's on the move.
After him.
Lightning creation magic!
Thunderbolt destruction!
Go flame magic!
Prison, death, scattershot!
Well, all right.
I didn't see that coming.
Our surprise attack worked.
Guess these guys aren't so tough after all, huh?
Yeah, too bad.
But at least there are lots of them, so smashing their kneecaps ought to keep us entertained for a while.
I want squads one and two to stay on the target.
So you're in charge here?
The sooner this is over with, the sooner I can visit Marie.
See how you like my mirror magic.
Reflect refrain.
What's going on here?
I got a nap to finish, so let's make this quick.
Dark magic.
Dark, look!
Lightless Slash!
I don't care who you are.
Nobody ever lays a hand on my food!
Hey, numbskulls.
Save some of the fun for me.
A water barrier.
It's not meant to block attacks from out here,
but to keep their own spells from destroying the place?
You're the CO?
Fonzo, then you, if you care about our hostage at all, you better get your traitor's hands off me.
A hostage?
Who?
Don't me not take code.
Mariella's on her way now.
You may not have known where she had gone into hiding, but we did.
Now let me go.
Whoa-wee!
Captain Yami is so amazing.
Everything's playing out exactly like he said it would.
What?
My squad mates are going via portal to visit a lady by the name of Domina.
I don't think your hostage will be a hostage for much longer.
Who are you?
How long were you going to wait to come and get me?
A poor helpless woman hiding from a bunch of killers, and you just leave me here?
You're lucky I'm still alive, you useless jerk!
I was so worried.
When you didn't come looking for me, I thought you might have gotten hurt.
I'm a little more hurt now.
Thank you for bringing him.
I know I threw in a little extra, but I never thought you'd do this.
I guess that means Bruce was right about you all along.
I should have known.
I'm not so sure.
And this young man must be Asta.
You know about me?
I heard you were a tough-looking kid, and it seems like it's true.
From who?
Well...
What are you doing here?
Hmm?
I don't plan to hurt anyone.
Besides, how much damage can one girl possibly do on her own?
You beat up your teacher and tried to kidnap him!
Why should we trust you?
My intentions are in no way malicious.
I am simply using you.
What do you mean?
I recognize those robes.
You're the Black Bulls squad, aren't you?
Didn't Mariela know that when she ordered us to attack?
Hold on, you're telling us you sent your own men to storm the Black Bulls' hideout,
hoping they'd get crushed?
Meanwhile, I came here to the Black Market and informed Domina that Master Fonzel would
be arriving soon.
I wanted to ensure she was prepared.
However, I didn't expect you to get here so quickly.
This is a map.
I've researched escape routes and plotted them on it.
I don't understand why you would do this, though.
Nor I.
To strike a blow against the Diamond Kingdom.
A number of their assassins are now out of commission.
Master Fonzel and Domina will be able to escape.
So in other words, I set a plan in motion that would badly damage the organization.
This is revenge.
Mine against those who have controlled me.
Why now?
Much like my teacher, I'm tired.
I can't do what they ask of me anymore.
That said, I don't believe I have the strength to stay on the run for my whole life.
It wasn't easy, but I made a decision.
Exact my revenge and then turn myself into the Clover Kingdom's magic knights.
You were going to turn yourself in?
I was nearby, waiting for the circumstances to properly align.
I watched as Master Fonzel approached the Black Bull's hideout and saw him dragged inside.
I thought if I sent those troops against you, you would annihilate them for me.
Thank you for consulting us.
She makes it sound so easy.
And now, will you please take me into custody?
Then we all get what we want.
Think about this, Nariela.
Do you know what you're asking?
You could be subjected to extreme punishment.
The Clover Kingdom won't forget your past crimes.
And the organization can still reach you, even if you're in somebody else's custody.
I'm willing to accept that.
Yes, as long as my life is spared.
I've been thinking about what you said.
We have to find our own hope, our own reason for living.
Right?
Yeah, what about it?
It was obnoxious and overbearing.
That said, it was also moving.
And sort of dashing.
Oh, you think so?
Whatever punishment I might receive is the price I have to pay to atone for my crimes and begin a new life.
So no matter how severe it is, I'll bear it without complaint.
I see.
I've had enough of this!
Galio, sir, you're the Assassin Corps' commander and you've abandoned your troops.
That's horrible.
And what do you call what you did?
If you want so desperately to be executed, I can oblige you.
Everybody run.
He may sound like a petty fool who's just full of hot air, but his magic's quite tricky.
That's right!
Spatial creation magic!
Unopening red roof!
Now, Spatial creation magic!
Go, Riftmen!
But what are these creepy red guys?
And why's the room all red?
Galio's initial spell created this place.
And those figures are magic soldiers that can only exist here.
They're not going to be easy to beat.
But wait, hold on.
You jumped in front of the spell without knowing what it did?
If that had been offensive magic he was using, you could have died.
Are you stupid?
Well, maybe.
So what if I am?
I'd rather be stupid than just stand back and watch somebody die!
And besides, something's changed since the last time we saw each other.
I'm Asta of the Black Bulls now!
But I'm still your enemy.
I don't care!
This is who I am!
If someone needs help, I'll help them as much as I want!
You got it?
But hey, if you want to give me some backup while I'm at it, I won't mind!
I may not be as altruistic as he is, but I can't stand by and watch a student suffer.
So come on, let's work together and get through this!
Get through this?
How can we?
Easy!
This is nothing!
No, impossible!
Yeah, Knight's Headquarters, this is Yami of the Black Bulls.
We got a bunch of troublemakers rounded up out here.
Come and get him, would you?
That's a lot of mages to have hunting you.
Who is this Fonzel person and what did he do to get so many people sicked on him?
Wait, hold on.
Don't you mean Zell?
No, according to Gray, his full name is actually Fonzel.
Ah, that's right, he's Fonzel Kruger.
He was the commander of the Diamond Kingdom's invading army.
I met the guy on the battlefield a really long time ago.
Seriously?
I heard he moved from commanding the army to training their soldiers, but I guess he must
have deserted, which would explain why everybody and their mom was trying to get to him.
I realize it isn't my place to ask this, sir.
And correct me if I'm wrong, but did we just help a high-ranking member of our greatest
enemy's military escape?
Sounds about right.
McGauch?
Yes, Captain?
Never speak of this again.
My lips are sealed.
Please give me a week of Marie leave.
You're only supposed to see her once a month, aren't you?
I'll watch her so surreptitiously for all 168 hours that nobody will know.
Man, you've got some serious issues.
And so, the case of the creepy naked man and the mysterious attack on the Black Bull's
hideout was put to rest at last.
Are you sure it's okay for us to leave like this?
I'm worried that it'll only cause all of you more trouble in the long run if we just
up and vanish.
Captain Yami didn't have any problems with you guys going, so I'm sure it's fine.
Don't you think so?
Yes, sure.
Not fine, and it'll probably turn into something extremely not fine.
Are you sure you're okay with this, though?
Mariella isn't exactly the nicest person.
All the terrible things I did were under duress.
Galeo and his assassin corps were going to kidnap me and hold me hostage.
She's the one who put a stop to that, remember?
Besides, if you think about it, Mariella here is the reason my cell and I were reunited.
Honestly, there's such a thing as being too nice, you know?
You're one to talk, you and your pushover squad.
Honestly, I manipulated all of you so easily, it was ridiculous.
I never asked for your help, and I don't need it.
I can get by just fine without anybody else.
The only person you need in your life is you.
You've been telling yourself that for a while, huh?
Taking on the burden alone is actually surprisingly easy, isn't it?
You just keep saying to yourself as long as you can get through it, you'll be fine.
There's no need to consider the people around you.
So there's not really much thinking involved at all.
I hate to tell you, but that's off the table now.
Because once you have people in your life who care about you,
your problems and your decisions aren't only your own anymore.
That's right.
Now you've got to think about them, too.
So you better get used to it.
I guess I'm not the only one here with personality issues.
Well, it's not like I care what you think anyway.
All right, we should get going or it's going to be too hard.
Hey, there's nothing to cry about.
Remember, old man, you and me are guys who like to get things done.
And like you said, there's no time for sitting around, so get to work.
Go out there and make Domina as happy as you can.
You're right.
I was given more time when I thought I had none left, and I won't waste it.
Together, Mariela, Domina, and I are going to live life to the fullest.
That's the spirit!
All right, once things settle down a bit.
Great!
Take care of yourself!
Uh, and, well, I hate to ask this, but, uh, remember how you all thought I was a creep,
but then I told you I was actually robbed and my clothes were taken?
You're kidding, right?
Do you think I could borrow some money?
We should have just let the Diamond Kingdom have you!
And that's the story of how Fonzel, Domina, and Mariela met the Black Bulls.
Back in the present, Noel and Finral have called on Fonzel,
hoping he might be able to help them find a way to heal Asta's arms.
Domina, Mariela, how have you...
Enough with the naked thing!
You're a grown man!
Keep your clothes on!
Ow!
Stop!
It's not my fault!
These things are supposed to happen to me!
The house has already run down enough.
Don't contribute to its sorry state.
Oh, wow.
Poor Asta.
That's terrible.
He's had quite an eventful life for someone who's still so young.
His bad luck is inversely proportional to his height.
Do you have any ideas?
We have to find a way to heal him.
Anything will be helpful.
So, ancient hex magic, huh?
Well, there is one place.
My homeland, the Forest of Witches.
You think they'd help?
The Queen of the Witches' magic would.
Hey!
The smartest witch ever to grace the land of witches has come back to say hello!
I have business here, so open up!
Okay.
THE KINDBAT
Thank you.